[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This musical group debuted on Saturday Night Live in 1978 and released an album called Briefcase Full of Blues that same year.", "correct_answer": "The Blues Brothers", "incorrect_answers": ["Sunglasses and Briefcases", "Dead Men Walking", "The Killer Bees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries joined the United Nations organization in 2006?", "correct_answer": "Montenegro", "incorrect_answers": ["South Korea", "Poland", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these countries exports the most coffee per year?", "correct_answer": "Brazil", "incorrect_answers": ["Colombia", "Viet Nam", "Ethiopia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A marmite is a large circular sieve made with bamboo and mesh.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following asteroids is the only one visible to the naked eye?", "correct_answer": "Vesta", "incorrect_answers": ["Davida", "Ceres", "Pallas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Oyster mushrooms are used to treat what medical condition?", "correct_answer": "High cholesterol levels", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver disease", "Viral infections", "Measles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which continents (landmasses, not peripheral islands) are entirely in the Northern Hemisphere?", "correct_answer": "North America, Europe, and Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["North America and Europe", "Europe, Africa and Asia", "North America, Africa, and Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which U.S. state is the largest producer of blueberries in the world?", "correct_answer": "Maine", "incorrect_answers": ["Montana", "New York", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What King of England was nicknamed the Lionheart because of his reputation as a brave military leader and warrior?", "correct_answer": "Richard I of England", "incorrect_answers": ["Richard III of England", "William I of England", "Henry II of England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Charlie Chaplins most popular film character, who was voted one of the greatest movie heroes by the American Film Institute?", "correct_answer": "The Tramp", "incorrect_answers": ["The Wanderer", "The Idler", "The Bum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What has happened to Kelly during the four years of Chucks Cast Away?", "correct_answer": "She got married", "incorrect_answers": ["She waited for Chuck and they married", "She couldnt take the pain and passed away", "She committed suicide"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was popcorn first introduced in movie theaters?", "correct_answer": "1912", "incorrect_answers": ["1929", "1935", "1900"]}]